# **SAARTH KURLE**

saarthk11@gmail.com | (628)219-6916 | LinkedIn | GitHub | Website

## **Summary**

As a hardworking and results oriented Web Developer and trained in Full Stack Engineering & ML, I bring a wealth of experience in software development. My expertise extends across the full software development lifecycle, from concept and design to implementation and optimization.

### Skills

- Javascript w/ MERN Stack
- Python w/ Data Science
- Java

Remote

- MySQL
- Machine Learning
- CSS

## **Experience**

11/2023 - Current The Social Sundays New York, NY -

#### **Web Designer and Developer**

#### (Part-Time)

- At The Social Sundays, a dynamic startup, I thrive as a part-time Web Designer and Developer.
- I specialize in creating visually appealing and functionally robust websites.
- My role involves translating conceptual designs into responsive and user-friendly websites, ensuring an engaging online presence for our clients.

08/2022 - 01/2023

CyberCoders San Francisco, CA

#### **Staff Software Engineer**

#### (Part-Time)

- Worked with a team of 4 engineers on the technical implementation of a web-based platform for a healthcare client, enabling real-time patient data management and collaboration among healthcare providers.
- Created an enterprise-level CRM system for a financial services company. Technologies Used: Node.js, MongoDB, React.js, Java, Spring, PostgreSQL.

10/2021 - 08/2022

#### **Front Desk Assistant**

Campus Housing - SFSU

San Francisco, CA

- Assisted residents in various problem-solving scenarios at the front desk of a student dorm building.
- Provided exceptional customer service to ensure a positive living experience for all residents.

06/2021 - 07/2021

Kamal Classes Mumbai, India

#### **Java Developer Apprenticeship**

- Completed a Full Stack Advanced Java training program with SQL, JSP, Hibernate Framework and OCJA.
- Completed a MySQL Connected JDBC application with Swings for GUI and JFreecharts as a Final Project.

# **Education and Training**

Expected in 05/2024 **Bachelor of Science** in Computer Science San Francisco, CA San Francisco State University

# **Certifications**

- AWS Certified Machine Learning & Cloud Computing.
- Python for Data Science and AI IBM.